[{"question": " pheebs, can you help me pick out an engagement ring for monica? i can&#146;t figure this out! it&#146;s so hard! should i get her a  tiffany cut or a princess cut or a&#151;ah-ah! paper cut!", "answer": " now, have you told anyone else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " no, i don&#146;t want to tell anybody else because i don&#146;t want monica to find out.", "answer": " you told me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " well, it&#146;s because i trust you, you&#146;re one of my best friends, and you walked in on me when i was looking at ring brochures.", "answer": " yeah well, once again not knocking pays off. i only wish you hadn&#146;t been on the toilet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! so chandler, wanna go to the coffeehouse?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh all right.", "answer": " yeah, coffeehouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " oh perfect, we were just gonna see if you wanted to go.", "answer": " oh well, we don&#146;t because we got&#133;the&#133;other pl-place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " how rude.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. you wanna bite?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " so how are things going with paul?", "answer": " good. although y&#146;know, he-he&#146;s a private guy. y&#146;know, i wish i could get him to open up a little bit, share some feelings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " that&#146;s easy! you just have to think of him as a-as a jar of pickles that won&#146;t open.", "answer": " so what are you saying; i should run him under hot water and bang his head against a table?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " no that&#146;s what you do when you want to get the truth out of someone.", "answer": "  hi honey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": "  watch this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  how are you?", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hi paul!", "answer": " hi phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " so how are things going with you?", "answer": " can&#146;t complain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  come on.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " great to see you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " good to see you too!", "answer": " how you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey pheebs, what-what was the deal with you and chandler blowing us off before?", "answer": " yeah! that was so weird, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " phoebe, why&#146;d you do it?", "answer": " i didn&#146;t do it! it was chandler! he&#146;s&#133; he&#146;s mad at you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " what?! why?!", "answer": " please, i think you know why.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i can&#146;t think of anything.", "answer": " come on ross, you&#146;re a paleontologist, dig a little deeper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " wait a minute, is it because joey and i didn&#146;t invite him to that knicks game a couple of weeks ago?", "answer": " do you think that&#146;s something that he&#146;d be mad at you for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i guess it could.", "answer": " well then i think that&#146;s it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " well, if he&#146;s angry, he really shouldn&#146;t just cover it up. i-i wish he would just tell me the truth.", "answer": " oh, if that&#146;s what you want you then you really should run his head under hot water and bang his head against a table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " honey i made a reservation at china garden, is that okay?", "answer": " yeah that&#146;s great. but first, wait, talk to me, talk to me. tell me about your day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " it was fine.", "answer": " okay. hey, what are you thinking? what are you thinking right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i&#146;m thinking that you are looking really fine it that dress.", "answer": " yeah that&#146;s great paul, but y&#146;know i wanna know what&#151;&#151;wow, those are really great! i just wanna know what, what is behind this-this strong, silent exterior. y&#146;know they say that still waters run deep and i wanna swim in yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " are you talking about having sex?", "answer": " no paul, i don&#146;t know anything about you! y&#146;know, like-like your childhood! tell me about your childhood!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " normal.", "answer": " okay, well then how about puberty! come on, that&#146;s always a painful time! y&#146;know your friends invite you to a slumber party and then they stick your hand in warm water while you&#146;re sleeping so that you pee in your sleeping bag.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " nope! that never happened to me!", "answer": " well, you&#146;re lucky you never met that bitch sharon majesky. anyway, umm&#133; the rest of you life, y&#146;know? any regrets?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " nope.", "answer": " all right paul, i&#146;m not asking for a lot here. okay? just give me something. anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " when i was six years old.", "answer": " hm-mmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i wanted a big wheel. and instead my parents got me this little plastic chicken that you hop around on. it was embarrassing; kids made fun of me. that was a pretty tough year.", "answer": " that&#146;s-that&#146;s great! see? i already feel like i know you a little better! thank you. okay, come on. now we can go eat. let&#146;s go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " it was horrible. they called me chicken boy.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " and in fifth grade i got into a fight. well, it wasn&#146;t really a fight. richard darinvel bit me on the nose and, and i feel down. i still have a little scare right here  you can see it.", "answer": " yeah. yeah, i-i-i see the scare. listen, paul, i think this is really great that-that y&#146;know, you shared your feelings. it&#146;s really, it&#146;s beautiful, but umm, what do you say we go share some food?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " oh, i couldn&#146;t eat now.", "answer": " what?! wait! what are you talking about?! you love their kung pao chicken!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " chicken?  chicken boy!", "answer": " my god, i&#146;m sorry! i&#146;m sorry! i didn&#146;t mean to do that! i wouldn&#146;t do that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " okay, so maybe you don&#146;t get her a ring. maybe you-maybe you do something different. y&#146;know? maybe you get her an engagement bracelet, y&#146;know? or an engagement tiara? or&#151;ooh! an engagement revolutionary war musket! (picks one up from the display in the corner.", "answer": " y&#146;know, i&#146;m so glad i picked you to help me with this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " huh? can you just imagine getting down on one knee and handing her this gorgeous piece of weaponry?", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m gonna stick with the ring.  oh, this one&#146;s nice!  i like this one! sir? uh, kind sir? can i see this one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  wait a minute, no, this is, this is the reason you brought me. okay? i know how to haggle. so let me handle this from here on out.", "answer": " can i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " uh-uh, yes. i would like to see that ring please.", "answer": " or not, whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " this ring is from the 1920s, it&#146;s a one and a half carat diamond with sapphires on either side.", "answer": " sir, can i ask you to umm, could you&#133;hold out that ring and ask me to marry you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay.  will you marry me?", "answer": "  oh my god that&#146;s it, that&#146;s the ring! how much is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " chandler, i-i will handle this!  how much is it?", "answer": " 8,600.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " we will give you $10.", "answer": "  are you interested in this ring?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " yes! yes, but i can only pay $8,000.", "answer": " okay, i can let it go at eight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " we stand firm at $10.", "answer": "  how would you like to pay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " uh, credit card.  oh no! no-no, but i left my credit card with joey.  okay, i&#146;ll go get it. you guard the ring.", "answer": " okay.  listen, i&#146;m sorry about before. do you have anything her for $10.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey, remember how chandler and phoebe blew us off yesterday?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " remember? you-you were eating pizza.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " okay. well, apparently chandler&#146;s angry at us for not getting him a ticket to that knicks game a couple of weeks ago.", "answer": " oh, we&#146;re supposed to just get him a ticket?! that guy is always mooching off of us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah! anyway, i-i still think we should try to patch things up, y&#146;know? like uh, maybe we could get him to get tickets to another knicks game and invite him.", "answer": " oh wow that&#146;s a great idea! and i still have his credit card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  here you go.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey-hey-hey-ho-ho, i got this one. here you go.  y&#146;know i gotta tell ya, sometimes i just&#151;i don&#146;t get chandler. y&#146;know, me and him do stuff all the time without you and you don&#146;t get all upset.", "answer": " all the time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh my god! oh my god!!", "answer": " still crying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " like a little girl. i know. i know. i know. this is all my fault; i wanted him to open up. but god, i didn&#146;t know that i was gonna unleash this-this weepy, clingy, moist monster!", "answer": " y&#146;know, i only know of two surefire ways to shut a man up. and one of them is sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what&#146;s the other one?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, i&#146;ve never had to use the other one. i&#146;m just saying y&#146;know, if we&#146;re having sex, he&#146;s not gonna be talking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s right. you&#146;re the talker.  anyway uh, great idea! umm, i gotta go to the store; i told him that i would buy him some more tissues.", "answer": " oh, we have some&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay umm, i&#146;d also like to try on the tiara.  oh yeah. okay.   what do you think, too much?", "answer": " a tad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " okay. then, take the tiara back and let me hold the musket again.  something&#146;s missing. it&#146;s not&#133; okay oh, let me see the ring my friend picked out.", "answer": "  where&#146;s the 1920s princess cut ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " rachel?", "answer": " no. how are ya paul?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  okay. chandler, did your dad ever hug you?", "answer": " no, did he hug you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " no! no! it&#146;s just that, my dad never did. i miss my dad.", "answer": " well, you can see my dad in vegas kissing other dads.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hey chandler?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " would you&#133;&#133;.would you hug me?", "answer": " i&#146;m a little busy here paul.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " five more seconds.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " do you have my credit card?", "answer": " yes, it&#146;s in my&#133; in&#133;in my pocket.   my back pocket! my back pocket!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh hey listen i got us tickets to a knicks game tonight.", "answer": " oh, i can&#146;t go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh, that&#146;s uh, that&#146;s pretty nice but i&#146;m gonna go with the one i picked first.", "answer": " oh my god chandler, the one you picked is gone. it&#146;s over!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " some guy bought it. i&#146;m sorry. i tired to stop it but they  put me in jail!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " they put you in jail?", "answer": " the little jail between the doors!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " phoebe, i asked you to guard the ring!", "answer": " i know, i&#146;m sorry! but y&#146;know, this ring is better! monica never even saw the other ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " yeah but when he proposed to me with the ring i got goose bumps.", "answer": " maybe it was the guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " hey! so uh, was he excited about the tickets?", "answer": " no! he blew us off!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe it.  can i tell you something? i&#146;m a little mad at him now.", "answer": " can i tell you something? me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? he didn&#146;t want to talk to us about being angry, well maybe we don&#146;t talk to him at all!", "answer": " ooooh! freeze him out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " that&#146;s right!", "answer": " i like it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " eh? we&#146;ll show him!", "answer": " from now on, it&#146;s gonna be joey and ross, best friends.  okay! we&#146;re gonna be the new joey and chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hi. i&#146;m back.", "answer": " hey! i have so much more to tell ya, i&#146;ve written it all down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " ah that&#146;s great. no actually that&#146;s&#133;  that&#146;s great! that&#146;s really great! y&#146;know, i gotta tell ya writing, i mean writing, gets me uh, gets me kinda hot.", "answer": " wait! wait! listen! listen to this!  y&#146;know what i wanted to be when i was that age?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " a lover?", "answer": " a surfer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh yeah surfer?", "answer": " i wanted to be one with the waves, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay, hold on real quick, hold on a second let me just uh,  get a little more comfortable here. wait, now wait a second, this isn&#146;t too revealing is it?", "answer": "  no. what ever happened to that little dude.  so full of dreams&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " i don&#146;t care about the little dude! i can&#146;t! i cannot listen to anymore of this! y&#146;know, the only person who would want to listen to this is a mental health professional! and then it&#146;s only because they get paid $100 an hour! do you know how much money i could&#146;ve made listening to you? $2,000! and do you know when i figured that out? while you were talking!", "answer": " what?! i can&#146;t believe you&#146;re trying to stifle me! when just 14 hours ago we figured out that that is exactly what my mother was trying to do to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " oh&#133; i&#146;m sorry. i&#133; i-i don&#146;t mean&#151;i didn&#146;t mean to stifle you. i&#133; this is all just a little overwhelming.", "answer": " oh rachel, i&#146;m so sorry. i didn&#146;t mean to overwhelm you. it&#146;s just that, when those gates open, you&#133;  hard to close &#145;em. but they are closed now. believe me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " i can&#146;t believe i let you talk me into buying this stupid gumball machine looking ring!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " it&#146;s not a stupid gumball machine looking ring! it&#146;s a beautiful ring!", "answer": " no, it&#146;s not! when i looked at the other ring i could see monica&#146;s face when i gave it to her, y&#146;know? and i could see her saying yes. when i look at this ring, all i see is a ring! unless i look at it really closely and then i can see my own eye.  look, this is the most important thing i&#146;m gonna do in my life. i wanna make sure it&#146;s perfect.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " okay. there may be a way that we can get the other ring back. &#145;cause i heard the guy tell the jeweler where he was going to propose. so maybe we can get him to trade rings or something.", "answer": " i can&#146;t do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " okay and he hasn&#146;t proposed yet because she has no ring on her finger.", "answer": " wow! you&#146;re good! after this, we should solve crimes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah! okay, go, go, go get him.", "answer": " oh, okay.  excuse me sir? could you come with me please? you have a phone call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " who is it?", "answer": " it is your office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " do you know who at my office?", "answer": " john?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  here he is.", "answer": "  hi! hi. okay, there was a slight mix-up at the jewelry store, the ring you&#146;re about to propose with was supposed to be held for me. so, i&#146;m gonna need to have that back.  but, in exchange i&#146;m willing to trade you this beautiful, more expensive ring.  ew.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " wow! i would trade.", "answer": " it is beautiful, but i&#146;m gonna use this one. now, if you&#146;ll excuse me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no-no! this is my fiancee  and her heart was set on that ring. you don&#146;t want to break her heart now do you?", "answer": " yeah, do you want to break a dying woman&#146;s heart?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yeah, she&#146;s dying&#133; of a cough apparently.", "answer": " yes, and it is my dying wish to have that ring. see, if i&#146;m not buried with that ring then my spirit is going to wander the nether world for all eternity&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  okay, that&#146;s enough honey!", "answer": " i don&#146;t know.  let me see the ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " guys?  i&#146;ve got something important to tell ya.  guys?  guys?!  i&#146;m gonna ask monica to marry me.", "answer": "  i think we gotta end the freeze out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " wait a minute, is this, is this for real?", "answer": " yeah, check out the ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh my god!!", "answer": " so you two are really serious?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " yep, pretty much.", "answer": " you-you&#146;re gonna get married?! i mean&#133; we&#146;re gonna be brothers-in-law!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " and-and-and-and-and-and, and we&#146;re gonna be friends again!", "answer": "  heyyyy&#151;what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh it&#146;s water under the bridge, forget it!", "answer": " okay!  i was gonna wait &#145;til uh, it was official y&#146;know? but i got so excited i just had to tell you guys because you&#146;re my best friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i think i&#146;m gonna cry!", "answer": "  ugh! no more crying! please! i just dumped one cry baby, i&#146;ll dump you too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna ask monica to marry me.", "answer": " oh my god! oh my god! oh chandler!!  you guys are gonna be so happy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": "  where&#146;s all the tissues?!  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " check out the ring.", "answer": "  nice! one and a half carat easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": "  hi.", "answer": " hey-hey pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " chandler&#146;s gonna ask monica to marry him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " you told her before you told us?", "answer": " well, she walked in when i was looking at the ring brochures. you can understand that, right?  guys? guys?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]